

## CONTACT

ingenieroabnersaavedra@gmail.com

+58 424 317 4308

Lara, Venezuela.

in linkedin.com/in/abner-saavedra/

## ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

- Informatics Engineer UCLA Venezuela, 2016.
- SAP MM academy training. Core consultants, 2016.
- Certification in English. Alpha Language Center, 2016.

#### LANGUAGES

- Spanish: native.
- English: intermediate
- Italian: basic

## EXPANDED CURRICULUM

abnersaavedra.github.io/CV/

#### OTHER INTERESTS

- Public speaking workshop.
- UCLA Venezuela, 2015. Extension of culture.
- Popular guitar course.
- UCLA Venezuela, 2011. Extension of culture.

# ABNER SAAVEDRA

# INFORMATICS ENGINEER

## **ABOUT ME**

Informatics engineer with more than 7 years of experience in software development, both in the visual part and on the server side (fullstack developer). I have participated in various developments that include web pages, virtual stores, web and mobile applications, having the opportunity to lead and coordinate work teams on different occasions.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# NodeJS/Angular fullstack developer.

Ragatex, October 2022 - January 2023.

- I created and implemented a data model.
- I developed REST API services.
- I integrated and consumed REST API services.
- Did testing and debugging of REST API services.
- I created and integrated software components.
- I debugged and improved existing functionalities.
- I did web layout.
- I did continuous integration of advances.

## Fullstack Java developer.

UCLA Venezuela, 2015-2016.

- I belonged to the TEIDE information system development team for the Canario Larense Club.
- I collected information inherent to the organization's procedures, processes and activities.
- I carried out requirements analysis.
- I applied requirements engineering.
- I developed software solutions that supported the execution of management, processes and core and support activities within the organization.

## Instructor of technological initiation program.

Simoncito UPEL. Barquisimeto - Lara, Venezuela.

August 2013 - February 2014.

• I served as an instructor of the Technological Initiation Program for early education children (PITNEI).